{"questions": [
	{"questionNumber" : 1,
		"questionText" : "What color is the sky?",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			"Red",
			"Green",
			"Yellow",
			"Blue"
		],
		"correctAnswer": 4
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 2,
		"questionText" : "Earth is the what planet of the solar system?",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "First",
				"answer2": "20th",
				"answer3": "Third",
				"answer4": "Only"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 3
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 3,
		"questionText" : "You are viewing this on a type of computer",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "True",
				"answer2": "False",
				"answer3": "",
				"answer4": ""
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 4,
		"questionText" : "Which of these is NOT one of the SEVEN dwarves in Snow White?",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "Silly",
				"answer2": "Grumpy",
				"answer3": "Doc",
				"answer4": "Sneezy"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 5,
		"questionText" : "What is the minimum number of wheels a CAR should have?",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "1",
				"answer2": "2",
				"answer3": "3",
				"answer4": "4"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 4
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 6,
		"questionText" : "Fill in the blank: Ice tends to be ______.",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "Cold",
				"answer2": "squisy",
				"answer3": "cold",
				"answer4": "burning"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 3
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 7,
		"questionText" : "Fill in the blank: And I would have gotten away with it too, if it weren't for you ______ !",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "meddling kids",
				"answer2": "stinky kids",
				"answer3": "barking dogs",
				"answer4": "quacking cats"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 8,
		"questionText" : "Which of these was NOT a Warner Bros from Animaniacs?",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "Wakko",
				"answer2": "Dot",
				"answer3": "Hello Nurse",
				"answer4": "Yakko"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 3
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 9,
		"questionText" : "Mickey from Disney is a ____?",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "abberation",
				"answer2": "mouse",
				"answer3": "house",
				"answer4": "louse"
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 2
	},
	{"questionNumber" : 10,
		"questionText" : "JavaScript is fun!",
		"possibleAnswers": [
			{"answer1": "True",
				"answer2": "False",
				"answer3": "",
				"answer4": ""
			}
		],
		"correctAnswer": 1
	}
]}